Beyond War. Beyond Hell. Beyond the Grave.
The Bunker is a horror, mystery, drama film directed by Rob Green.
In 1944, in the Belgian - German border, seven German soldiers survive an American
attack in the front and lock themselves in a bunker to protect the position.
Under siege by the enemy and with little ammunition, they decide to explore
underground tunnels to seek supplies and find an escape route.
While in the tunnel, weird things happen with the group.
Cpl. Baumann, played by Jason Flemyng.
Cpl. Schenke, played by Andrew Tiernan.
Sgt. Heydrich, played by Christopher Fairbank.
Lt. Krupp, played by Simon Kunz.
Pvt. Neumann, played by Andrew-Lee Potts.
Pvt. Mirus, played by John Carlisle.
The Bunker is a 2001 war horror film directed by Rob Green,
written by Clive Dawson and starring Jason Flemyng.
The film explores themes of nazi, world war ii, bunker, soldier, ardennes.
The tone is dark and emotional and mind_bending.